<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>James Addison</title><link href="http://jamesaddison.ca/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://jamesaddison.ca/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://jamesaddison.ca/</id><updated>2015-06-17T11:00:00-07:00</updated><entry><title>Juce Communications First Impressions</title><link href="http://jamesaddison.ca/juce-communications-first-impressions/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-06-17T11:00:00-07:00</updated><author><name>James Addison</name></author><id>tag:jamesaddison.ca,2015-06-17:juce-communications-first-impressions/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#8217;re not aware, there&amp;#8217;s a bit of a &lt;a href="https://unblockcanada.ca/"&gt;tussle going on with regards to internet service pricing here in Canada&lt;/a&gt;. Given the situation, I thought I would explore other options - of which there are not very many in Canada, and fewer still here in Victoria, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;BC&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A like-minded friend recently switched from the local cable internet incumbent Shaw to a new local entrant by the name of &lt;a href="https://www.juce.ca/"&gt;Juce Communications&lt;/a&gt;. Although only recently started, he&amp;#8217;s happy with the service and pricing - and he&amp;#8217;s got a thing against Shaw. So, he&amp;#8217;s advocating others move to Juce&amp;#8230; which brings this story to&amp;nbsp;me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Juce&amp;nbsp;Overview&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Juce, based out of Victoria, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;BC&lt;/span&gt;, currently has two service plans: 25Mbps ($39.95/mo + taxes) and 50Mbps ($79.95/mo + taxes). No bandwidth capping. I believe they have plans to expand to cover most cable-ready regions of &lt;span class="caps"&gt;BC&lt;/span&gt; and&amp;nbsp;Alberta.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Juce is quite upfront about their billing policies (upfront billing), transfer and installation fees in their &lt;a href="https://www.juce.ca/"&gt;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;FAQ&lt;/span&gt; section on their site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#8217;re currently with Shaw, then there is a $22 transfer fee, otherwise there is a $79 installation fee (for example, if you switched from Telus, the local &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DSL&lt;/span&gt; incumbent provider). Why the difference? If you&amp;#8217;re not with Shaw already, it means you likely need to get the necessary cabling for the modem set up in your house, for one. Additionally, Shaw needs to do some &amp;#8216;provisioning&amp;#8217; (configuration) of modems on behalf of Juce, so having an existing Shaw account makes this easier, I&amp;nbsp;presume.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I figured it was time for me to upgrade anyhow, so on June 9th I chose the 50Mbps Juce&amp;nbsp;plan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Signing&amp;nbsp;up&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The online signup process was simple enough; I really only got bogged down when choosing which modem to get. I wanted to look up some reviews of their listed compatible models - here are the options Juce&amp;nbsp;provides:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I will use my own modem.&amp;nbsp;$0.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motorola &lt;span class="caps"&gt;SB6120&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DOCSIS&lt;/span&gt; 3.0 (Refurbished)&amp;nbsp;$35.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Motorola &lt;span class="caps"&gt;SB6141&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DOCSIS&lt;/span&gt; 3.0 (Motorola Refurbished)&amp;nbsp;$49.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thomson &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DCM475&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DOCSIS&lt;/span&gt; 3.0 (&lt;span class="caps"&gt;NEW&lt;/span&gt;)&amp;nbsp;$79.00&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I selected with the Motorola &lt;span class="caps"&gt;SB6141&lt;/span&gt; as reviews indicated it was the best compromise between cost and&amp;nbsp;quality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That same day I received a few emails: some invoicing/billing related and one with a tracking number for my modem. About two or three days later, I received the modem. On June 13th I received confirmation of my activation window which was to be on June 16th. It&amp;#8217;s unfortunate it takes a while to do this, but from my understanding a big part of the delay rests on Shaw&amp;#8217;s shoulders (scheduling provisioning,&amp;nbsp;etc).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both Shaw and Juce deliver services via Shaw&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8220;last mile&amp;#8221; stretch of network.  If you&amp;#8217;re like me and ordered a new/refurbished modem through Juce, then you simply need to wait for the modem to arrive (sent with a tracking number via Canada Post) and then plug it in, at which point Shaw (yes, Shaw - not Juce) needs to update the modem with a new configuration, telling it to communicate with the Juce&amp;nbsp;network.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you already have a working, compatible modem, the only thing necessary is for Shaw to update your modem&amp;#8217;s configuration to switch to&amp;nbsp;Juce.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And so the wait&amp;nbsp;began.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Activation and&amp;nbsp;Testing&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On my activation date of June 16th, I plugged the modem in. In a couple of minutes, it picked up the connection and everything was running via Juce. Literally, that&amp;#8217;s all there was to&amp;nbsp;it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, the story doesn&amp;#8217;t end here. Like any nerd, I load up a speed test website to test the new connection, and I get 21-22Mbps! Remember, I ordered the 50Mbps plan, so naturally I started raging and throwing my stuffed animals around. (Just kidding, I don&amp;#8217;t have any stuffies - not in my office&amp;nbsp;anyhow.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I sent a quick &amp;#8220;What&amp;#8217;s going on here&amp;#8221; email to their support team. Within minutes (awesome Juce!), I received a response explaining that the modem had been sent the wrong config. To correct things, they&amp;#8217;d sent a request to Shaw to update the modem to the correct config - and of course, this can take a few days for whatever the same reasons were that you have to wait activate in the first place (Shaw being slow to respond, a backlog in their teams, politics,&amp;nbsp;whatever).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But wait, my bad luck didn&amp;#8217;t end there! The new modem (actually, refurbished) dropped the connection entirely. I thought it was something to do with the incorrect config file, but after unplugging it a few times, I still had no luck.  Another email to the Juce support team (at&amp;nbsp;11:30pm)&amp;#8230;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the morning (June 17th), I got a reply from Juce saying they would send someone out to poke around for problems. The rep was courteous and apologetic on behalf of Juce - thank you! He got the modem working again, ran a speed test which showed speeds around 29Mbps - for the current 25Mbps plan, that was pretty good! He said that they &amp;#8220;over-provision&amp;#8221; to ensure customers get a good speed&amp;nbsp;experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shortly after, the modem dropped the connection again. Frustrating. At this point it was looking to be the modem itself - likely just a dud. The rep pulled another identical modem out of his bag and hooked it up - while it wasn&amp;#8217;t provisioned (no config file yet, meaning it couldn&amp;#8217;t provide a connection), the blinky lights showed more promise. The rep confirmed it was showing more promise than the initial modem, and said that he&amp;#8217;d leave it in place and put in the request with Shaw to have it provisioned (and with the correct speed of 50Mbps this&amp;nbsp;time).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Within two hours (still June 17th), I received an email from Juce support saying that I can plug the modem in, it will get provisioned and I can start hitting the internet over Juce&amp;#8217;s pipes. They clarified that it would still be at the 25Mbps speed until Shaw updated the configuration - which could take a few days as mentioned previously. I ran a quick speed test and saw 29Mbps - same as the rep when he had been here - so definitely more promising a start. It hasn&amp;#8217;t been long, but observationally I think it was a dud modem. I can&amp;#8217;t blame Juce for that. I can credit them with timely support/response times,&amp;nbsp;however!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Throughout the changeover, I hadn&amp;#8217;t cancelled my existing Shaw account. I wanted to give Juce a spin for a day or two and then cancel Shaw if things are smooth. I&amp;#8217;d definitely recommend this approach to others considering this switch - I wouldn&amp;#8217;t consider it as necessary if you were using your existing modem (you know it already works, after all)&amp;nbsp;however.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 25Mbps/50Mbps mixup may have been caused on either Juce&amp;#8217;s or Shaw&amp;#8217;s end, whether miscommunication or straight up error. Juce took care of me, however - they issued a refund of $10 to my account without question or prompting. That is more than you can say about many businesses out&amp;nbsp;there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, even through the difficulties I&amp;#8217;ve encountered, I&amp;#8217;m impressed with how Juce - a small and young company - has performed. I truly hope that they aren&amp;#8217;t squashed by the &lt;a href="https://cartt.ca/article/shaws-proposed-wholesale-broadband-rates-just-unreasonable-independent-isps-argue"&gt;incumbents&amp;#8217; political moves (trying to price out &amp;#8220;last mile&amp;#8221; resellers)&lt;/a&gt;. You should read that&amp;nbsp;article.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the time of this writing, it&amp;#8217;s only been a few hours since I&amp;#8217;ve switched over. I&amp;#8217;ll come back and update this post with anything further, particularly when I finally hop up to the 50Mbps&amp;nbsp;tier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Notes&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For reference, my existing Shaw service was an old 25Mbps plan (definitely capped), which doesn&amp;#8217;t seem to be publicly available anymore.  It was costing me $67/month + taxes - about $75/month&amp;nbsp;total.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Default Image Loading in Email Clients</title><link href="http://jamesaddison.ca/default-image-loading-in-email-clients/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2015-01-24T17:49:00-08:00</updated><author><name>James Addison</name></author><id>tag:jamesaddison.ca,2015-01-24:default-image-loading-in-email-clients/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;A quick post, just to ask the question: did email clients like iOS/&lt;span class="caps"&gt;OSX&lt;/span&gt; Mail and GMail change to displaying images by default (as opposed to blocking them) simply to make open stats in email list tools like Mailchimp more impressive than their&amp;nbsp;competition?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I&amp;#8217;m not mistaken, Apple was the first major player to make this move. (Correct me if I&amp;#8217;m&amp;nbsp;wrong!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If true, it&amp;#8217;s a clever way to manipulate businesses to shift marketing resources to focus more on the Apple&amp;nbsp;crowd.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If false, they did it to provide a better user experience, I surmise. That, and this post was a waste of time. Well, at least it was&amp;nbsp;short.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>My Startup Failure, 20 Lessons Learned</title><link href="http://jamesaddison.ca/my-startup-failure-20-lessons-learned/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-10-13T06:47:00-07:00</updated><author><name>James Addison</name></author><id>tag:jamesaddison.ca,2014-10-13:my-startup-failure-20-lessons-learned/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;No one wants to talk about their failures, yet it’s the most important way to learn and improve. Learning through doing is more about making mistakes as it is about repetition. The key is to look back and review: the&amp;nbsp;post-mortem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s a part of the startup game and it’s important to know that &lt;strong&gt;in the world of startups, failure is the norm - not the exception&lt;/strong&gt;. When you join a startup it’s important to acknowledge that you’re going to be out of your comfort&amp;nbsp;zone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In mid-2006, I joined what would become a failed startup venture. We officially dissolved the company in mid-2012, however in reality it had failed far earlier. I’d like to share some of my views on the&amp;nbsp;experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;TL&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;DR&lt;/span&gt; version? &lt;a href="#tldr"&gt;Click&amp;nbsp;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;In the&amp;nbsp;Beginning&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Three friends and former colleagues of mine approached me with an idea in the photo management software and online sharing space. They viewed the market as fragmented and poorly served, particularly in the ‘full-stack photo solution’. I generally agreed; we became the founders of Tecagora and created the product&amp;nbsp;Snapact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our team and share&amp;nbsp;structure:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business guy (28%): accounting, legal, sales/business&amp;nbsp;development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Business/Technology guy (24%): operating and some product&amp;nbsp;management/development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technology dude (24%): Windows software&amp;nbsp;development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technology dude (me, 24%): some Windows software dev but mostly server side web app&amp;nbsp;development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had no share/option vesting schedules or cliffs - just straight up percentage ownership. We bootstrapped the business and kept separate full-time jobs elsewhere. Naturally, evenings and weekends were meant for ‘starting&amp;nbsp;up’.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The product was photo management software for Windows tightly coupled to a web app for online photo sharing - and we were excited to bring this vision to&amp;nbsp;life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;The Long&amp;nbsp;Road&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We made some early assumptions on how we’d generate revenue, based on our collective prior experiences at other companies. Instead, we made the easy decision to focus on building the product right off the bat with little regard to&amp;nbsp;monetization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was also decided that adding features before launching was critical. It was important to us to have a product that did more than a minimal feature set. This left us with a really long roadmap to get anything to market. In short, our overall plan was: &lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0097351/"&gt;build it and they will come&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To be clear, our initial product vision wasn’t as feature-rich as the entrenched competition. However, we definitely should have simplified our initial product’s feature set further to get to market&amp;nbsp;quicker.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t remember exactly how long it took to get to launch day, but we were excited when we opened the doors to the public. We labeled Snapact ‘beta’ because it was the cool thing to do at the time with your new tech&amp;nbsp;baby.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both the software and the online photo sharing portal were free at launch; we uploaded the software on various free/shareware portals for&amp;nbsp;distribution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I seem to remember we decided to make the photo sharing service freemium: share up to 100 photos (or something like that), after that you’d need to upgrade. The photo manager client software remained&amp;nbsp;free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also briefly talked about looking for funding, but quickly decided we didn’t want to dilute our shares - besides, what could funding bring (if we could even get it) that we&amp;nbsp;needed?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Reality&amp;nbsp;Hits&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We had several thousand downloads over the lifetime of the product - notably, this isn’t a lot. Worse, we didn’t make it easy for users to give us feedback. This limited our ability to iterate and improve - we were reduced to guesses and assumptions. Never a good&amp;nbsp;thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some product reviews were written and published online - a few were surprises to us, most had been at our request/suggestion to pertinent sites. We managed to get placed on a software compilation disc distributed via a European non-english&amp;nbsp;magazine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite in-app prompting, few people were signing up for our online photo sharing service. You shouldn’t expect much from just a few software downloads/installs/users, when only a small fraction will sign up for a freemium&amp;nbsp;service.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eventually Google Adsense was added to shared photo pages. Revenue from this was - you guessed it - negligible. We tried working with 3rd party vendors to generate product sales - I don’t remember the specifics of this, but vendors quickly lost interest in pushing the distribution of Snapact. They’re commission-based and if people aren’t raving about the product it won’t generate sales - leaving them with little&amp;nbsp;incentive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I remember frustration, fear, anger and hopelessness at various points after the startup honeymoon and launch periods. While I truly enjoyed building the product, our team interaction began to feel strained. Remember, this was a bootstrapped company - it provided no income for any of us. It wasn’t even covering its own&amp;nbsp;costs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It began to feel like we allowed only consensus-driven decision-making, meaning we weren’t making critical decisions. We glossed over and tried to ignore important signals which, if we’d been attentive may have given us better&amp;nbsp;direction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Essentially, it felt&amp;nbsp;aimless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;So Many Lessons: &lt;span class="caps"&gt;TL&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;DR&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a class='fragment-link' name='tldr'&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your expectations, no matter how realistic they seem - are actually wildly&amp;nbsp;optimistic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don’t be secretive about your idea. Sure it’s your baby, but before you pour money and time into it, do your best to invalidate it - get outside&amp;nbsp;input.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don’t be wishy-washy. Make concrete decisions. No one should ever leave a discussion or meeting wondering what the outcome was or next steps&amp;nbsp;are.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Listen to your gut; recognize signals. Your subconscious is probably aware of various signals that you’re unwilling to&amp;nbsp;see.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set goals and measure progress towards those goals. If a goal isn’t on track then it’s either too optimistic or you need to consider another path. The end result is the same - you need to adjust. Worst case should be a&amp;nbsp;pivot.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don’t be afraid to walk away from a situation/startup/idea you’re not happy with. Move on to the&amp;nbsp;next.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always be inventive/innovative/ideating. Look outside your group - how are other people achieving success? Can you apply that to your&amp;nbsp;startup?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate outside your startup team. Discussing methods, tools, ideas, etc with others can only create stronger&amp;nbsp;output.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know how to grow a userbase. Maybe they won’t all succeed, but have an arsenal of strategies to deploy. This means researching, preparation and lead&amp;nbsp;time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Talk to your cofounders. Don’t sweep concerns under the rug, air your dirty laundry. Deal with things rather than bottling them&amp;nbsp;up.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Right from the beginning, formulate your funnel. Acquisition, sales, retention - they’re all important elements to factor&amp;nbsp;in.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advertising based revenue isn’t a foundation to build a business on. You need a massive monthly pageview count to make Adsense and the like&amp;nbsp;work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If something goes wrong, use &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/5_Whys"&gt;the 5 Whys&lt;/a&gt; to determine a course of action. Hell, if something goes right, use the 5 Whys to solidify what you should bake into your startup &lt;span class="caps"&gt;DNA&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don’t re-invent the wheel. Find a way to improve the wheel but make sure that people need your better&amp;nbsp;wheel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Charge your users from the beginning. You avoid awkward moments later when you want to add payments in. Crucially, you also discover whether you have a revenue model and product worth pursuing. It also means that bootstrapping can be&amp;nbsp;feasible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consider getting funding. Just the act of trying to get funding will reveal a mountain of wishful thinking on your part. (I’m all for bootstrapping, but going for funding really is an eye-opening&amp;nbsp;experience)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share/option vesting and cliffs aren’t a bad thing. It allows someone to walk away from the company without those who remain feeling ripped off. Everyone involved should feel&amp;nbsp;protected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Realize that whatever your thoughts for your &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MVP&lt;/span&gt; (minimal viable product) are, it’s probably still too much. Trim some more fat, then launch. Then iterate based on&amp;nbsp;feedback.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don’t bother with fancy C-level titles until well after there is someone to impress. I don’t mean users - investors and the like. Instead, you’re all founders trying to start something up. Keep the focus on&amp;nbsp;that.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you’re excited about something, you’re not thinking rationally. Take some time and don’t rush in. &lt;strong&gt;You need to think it&amp;nbsp;through.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Back to&amp;nbsp;Today&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I still look back at this startup with mixed emotions. I still remember that initial excitement and am still on the hunt for it again - but this time in a sustainable form. &lt;strong&gt;I learned an incredible amount from this failure&lt;/strong&gt;, and for this I am grateful to my former&amp;nbsp;cofounders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Life has since changed for each of us, but I’m still friends with them. We’ve all moved on to other projects and jobs and we all still have the startup&amp;nbsp;bug.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This retrospective is solely from my point of view, not representing the thoughts and opinions of my fellow co-founders. They likely view things&amp;nbsp;differently.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry><entry><title>Writing Habit Challenge</title><link href="http://jamesaddison.ca/writing-habit-challenge/" rel="alternate"></link><updated>2014-09-26T21:00:00-07:00</updated><author><name>James Addison</name></author><id>tag:jamesaddison.ca,2014-09-26:writing-habit-challenge/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Writing is hard. Writing well is&amp;nbsp;harder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve tried blogging before, but didn’t develop the necessary habit. I know that writing will help me learn as well as teach others. What better reasons are&amp;nbsp;there?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m using &lt;a href="http://www.literatureandlatte.com/scrivener.php"&gt;Scrivener&lt;/a&gt; as my blog post planning and drafting tool. It works well as a single contributor tool - and seeing how &lt;a href="http://jamesaddison.ca"&gt;jamesaddison.ca&lt;/a&gt; will only ever be my writing, it suits me&amp;nbsp;fine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog runs on &lt;a href="http://getpelican.com"&gt;Python-based software called Pelican&lt;/a&gt; and is currently hosted on &lt;a href="https://github.com/"&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;. This setup is not for the non-techie. The design is intentionally kept simple in an effort to keep focus on the content. Perhaps this will encourage me to publish quality&amp;nbsp;posts!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, with this post and this new site, I’m challenging myself to write every day. They won’t always be published posts, but snippets at the very least. I’m planning to keep this blog focused on startups and related topics, so if that’s your bag &lt;a href="/newsletter/"&gt;sign up for my newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to keep&amp;nbsp;updated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m optimistic: let’s see where it goes from&amp;nbsp;here.&lt;/p&gt;</summary></entry></feed>